The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
No matter how hard I try to suppress them,
I can't completely eradicate the demonic thoughts.
It seems I need to find another way.
Ancestor !
I've been in this Demon Spirit Land for a few years.
The local customs
and cultivation methods
are completely different from the outside world.
But some of the carvings here
are very similar to those of the ancient Celestial Realm.
Could it be...
that this place is the cultivation cave of a Celestial ?
If that's truly the case,
then all living beings here
are no different from livestock.
Heaven and earth show no mercy.
Whether it's here
or in the outside world...
it's all the same.
Customer,
our shop's green bamboo wine
is renowned across the 9 countries !
Would you like to try a cup ?
Ancestor
How many years has it been
since I last drank wine ?
It's been a while since the Heng Yue Sect
but we finally meet again !
Come on, cheers !
Zhang Hu...
Tie Zhu...
Father...
Mother...
No !
You're looking for death !
No...
Ancestor !
A single trace of demonic thoughts
actually caused my mind to lose control.
If I don't get rid of it now,
I'm afraid I won't be able to wake up.
But suppressing it with celestial spiritual energy
isn't very effective.
Gentlemen, please come inside !
Bring us your best dishes
and your best wine !
Faster than that !
Sima Yan\NBlack Armor Army Vice-Commander\NRank 100 000 demonic energy\N(Early stage Soul Transformation)
You bystanders
can scram !
Go, go, go !
Commander can rest assured !
Even if that man dares to come take his post,
the Black Armor Army won't acknowledge him !
Have you found out his background ?
Commander,
he's an outsider.
He couldn't even withstand the Demon General's Ten Collapse Battle Intent
but he was still granted the position of Commander.
You earned your Commander position through your own military merits.
It makes no sense for you
to be demoted because of this guy !
Exactly !
An outsider ?
Someone weaker than me
is unworthy of commanding me !
You clueless fools...
Scram now !
How dare you !?
Don't you dare disrespect the Ancestor !
Bold of you !
You're looking for death !
Get them !
This person is quite peculiar.
There are 2 completely different forces battling within him.
You savages...
How dare you cause trouble in Ancient Demon City !?
Ancestor !
The celestial and demonic energies within me are at a stalemate.
I can't break out of this state.
Perhaps an external stimulus can help me...
What's happening !?
I can't control my spear !
Could he be...
absorbing demonic energy ?
Withdraw demonic energy,
quick !
Ancestor ?
Ancestor, you're awake !
Take this.
Thank you, Ancestor !
Stop here !
We will meet again.
The celestial and demonic energies are incompatible,
making it hard to expel the demonic thoughts.
But by using the demonic energy outside my body, I was able to drive it out.
I managed to get out of this situation by a fluke.
These demonic thoughts can corrupt Dao Hearts,
they're impossible to guard against.
I'll refine and keep them for later,
I might find a use for them.
Ancestor,
someone requests an audience.
Enter.
I am Han Jin, military advisor of Ancient Demon City.
Han Jin\NAncient Demon City's military advisor
By order of the Demon General,
I'm here to escort Commander Wang to his assigned barracks.
He doesn't display his aura,
I can't quite see through his cultivation.
Please show me your Commander token.
Commander Wang,
please.
Black Armor Barracks\NAncient Demon City
Where is Sima Yan ?
By order of the Demon General,
I escort the newly appointed Commander Wang Lin to assume his post.
Vice-Commander Sima,
pay your respects.
Sima Yan pays his respects to Commander Wang.
We've already met.
Since you two know each other,
I won't disturb you any further.
I will take my leave
to report back to the Demon General.
Thank you for your trouble.
Commander Wang Lin,
the 10 000 soldiers of the Black Armor Army,
except for 3 who are unconscious,
are all present.
All of you are dismissed.
You're dismissed.
Understood !
Where did this coward come from ?
How dare he think he can command us ?
He should get the hell out of here !
I, Sima Yan, am the only Commander of the Black Armor Army.
Let's see how long you can last.
This is the Commander's tent,
how dare you block the way ?
This is Commander Sima's tent.
No trespassing is allowed !
Might I ask where the Vice-Commander's tent is ?
This is too much...
Ancestor,
since they're acting like this,
we should teach them a lesson !
Have you two memorized
the Sky Demon Country's Military Law ?
We will memorize it right away !
If a soldier defies orders,
it's that soldier's fault.
If 10 000 defy orders,
it's the Commander's fault.
If I act rashly, it will give them an excuse
and I will only lose my position as Commander
and end up wanted throughout the city.
Establishing authority
takes time.
He hasn't done anything for several days now.
What exactly is he planning ?
What do you think this Wang Lin
is actually scheming ?
It's pathetic,
he's just a worthless fool waiting to be slaughtered.
Sun Xiao\NBlack Armor Army Regiment Leader\NRank 10 000 demonic energy\N(Nascent Soul)
Regiment Leader Sun, I disagree.
This man remains completely unperturbed.
Yuan Shan\NBlack Armor Army Regiment Leader\NRank 10 000 demonic energy\N(Nascent Soul)
I'm afraid he is no ordinary person.
Old man Yuan,
that man unjustly took Commander Sima's position.
We were all nurtured by the Commander himself.
Don't diminish your own prestige
or try to drag us down with you.
You !
Enough !
Commander Sima is probably doing this out of respect for the Demon General.
He can't openly do anything against that Wang fellow.
But this Wang Lin is just a coward,
what is there to fear ?
If I can get rid of him for Commander Sima,
he will surely reward me...
Commander Wang,
I heard you have a broad mind
and are very tolerant.
He really doesn't care ?
He's simply...
trash !
Regiment Leader Sun,
what did you just say ?
I said you're tra...
Release the Regiment Leader !
Sky Demon Country's Military Law, Article 8.
Recite it !
Those who revolt
against their superior shall be...
beheaded !
You wouldn't dare!
Avenge the Regiment Leader !
Stubborn fools...
Stop !
How dare you harm my demon soldiers !?
This is outrageous !
Commander !
The Commander is here to settle this matter !
Do you also wish
to revolt against your superior ?
Wang Lin,
you killed a Regiment Leader and slaughtered demon soldiers !
We will not let this matter slide !
Thirteen,
Sky Demon Country's Military Law, Article 13.
Those who participate in a mutiny
have 10 breaths to disperse or shall be
beheaded !
Start counting.
Disperse !
Don't think you've won.
Vice-Commander Sima,
what urgent matter
did you summon me for ?
Commander Wang unjustly killed a Regiment Leader
and slaughtered demon soldiers.
I had no choice but to summon you
to enforce the Military Law !
Such a vicious slander.
Are there any witnesses ?
Wang Lin's methods are cruel.
The entire Black Armor Army
are witnesses.
Thirteen...
The entire sequence of events
is recorded in this jade.
You think before acting,
Commander Wang really is skilled.
Those who revolted against their superior
deserved to die.
I will now report this matter to the Demon General.
I, with 100 000 rank of demonic energy,
a Commander of the army,
have actually been trampled by an outsider !
Vice-Commander Sima,
commanding an army
lies in being impartial, fair,
and ensuring orders are followed.
Not in fighting amongst ourselves
or trying to be brave.
You'd better remember this.
This subordinate was reckless...
I beg Commander Wang's forgiveness !
You are not qualified
to be my enemy.
We pay respects to the Commander !
All of you are dismissed.
Understood !
Third Army Barracks\NAncient Demon City
I failed again...
If it weren't for the Blood Soul Pills,
Blood Soul Pills
I would have died 4 times already...
I don't have many chances left.
I must not fail in the task
that Father gave me.
If only I knew someone skilled in restrictions to help me,
I'm sure I would succeed in a single try.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?